Milne School; Records ua659
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Crimson and White Junior News, 1931 October 16-1941 May 24; 14; 0.4 cubic ft. 215 Digital Files
  - Junior News, 1932 March 4 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 1)
  - Junior News, 1932 March 11 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 1)
  - Junior News, 1932 March 18 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 1)
  - Junior News, 1932 April 8 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 1)
  - Junior News, 1932 April 15 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 1)
  - Junior News, 1932 April 22 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 1)
  - Junior News, 1932 April 29 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 1)
  - Junior News, 1932 May 6 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 1)
  - Junior News, 1932 May 13 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 1)
  - Junior News, 1932 May 19 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 1)
  - Junior News, 1932 May 27 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 1)
  - Junior News, 1932 October 7 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 1)
  - Junior News, 1932 October 14 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 1)
  - Junior News, 1932 October 21 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 1)
  - Junior News, 1932 October 28 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 1)
  - Junior News, 1932 November 4 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 1)
  - Junior News, 1932 November 11 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 1)
  - Junior News, 1932 November 23 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 1)
  - Junior News, 1932 December 2 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 1)
  - Junior News, 1932 December 16 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 1)
  - Junior News, 1932 December 21 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 1)
  - Junior News, 1933 January 13 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 1)
  - Junior News, 1933 January 20 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 1)
  - Junior News, 1933 January 27 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 1)
  - Junior News, 1933 February 10 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 1)
  - Junior News, 1933 February 17 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 1)
  - Junior News, 1933 February 24 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 1)
  - Junior News, 1933 March 3 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 1)
  - Junior News, 1933 March 10 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 1)
  - Junior News, 1933 March 17 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 1)
  - Junior News, 1933 March 24 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 1)
  - Junior News, 1933 March 31 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 1)
  - Junior News, 1933 April 7 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 1)
  - Junior News, 1933 April 28 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 1)
  - Junior News, 1933 May 5 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 1)
  - Junior News, 1933 May 18 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 1)
  - Junior News, 1933 May 26 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 1)
  - Junior News, 1933 June 2 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 1)
  - Junior News, 1933 October 6 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 1)
  - Junior News, 1933 October 13 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 1)
  - Junior News, 1933 October 20 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 1)
  - Junior News, 1933 October 27 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 1)
  - Junior News, 1933 November 3 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 1)
  - Junior News, 1933 November 10 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 1)
  - Junior News, 1933 November 17 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 1)
  - Junior News, 1933 November 24 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 1)
  - Junior News, 1933 December 8 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 1)
  - Junior News, 1933 December 15 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 1)
  - Junior News, 1934 January 12 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 1)
  - Junior News, 1934 January 12 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 1)
  - Junior News, 1934 January 19 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 1)
  - Junior News, 1934 January 19 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 1)
  - Junior News, 1934 February 9 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 1)
  - Junior News, 1934 February 9 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 1)
  - Junior News, 1934 February 23 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 1)
  - Junior News, 1934 February 23 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 1)
  - Junior News, 1934 March 2 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 1)
  - Junior News, 1934 March 2 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 1)
  - Junior News, 1934 March 9 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 1)
  - Junior News, 1934 March 16 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 1)
  - Junior News, 1934 March 16 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 1)
  - Junior News, 1934 March 22 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 1)
  - Junior News, 1934 March 22 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 1)
  - Junior News, 1934 March 23 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 1)
  - Junior News, 1934 April 13 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 1)
  - Junior News, 1934 April 20 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 1)
  - Junior News, 1934 April 20 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 1)
  - Junior News, 1934 April 27 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 1)
  - Junior News, 1934 April 27 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 1)
  - Junior News, 1934 May 4 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 1)
  - Junior News, 1934 May 4 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 1)
  - Junior News, 1934 May 11 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 1)
  - Junior News, 1934 May 11 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 1)
  - Junior News, 1934 May 25 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 1)
  - Junior News, 1934 June 1 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 1)
  - Junior News, 1934 June 1 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 1)
  - Junior News, 1934 October 5 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 1)
  - Junior News, 1934 October 5 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 1)
  - Junior News, 1934 October 12 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 1)
  - Junior News, 1934 October 12 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 1)
  - Junior News, 1934 October 26 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 1)
  - Junior News, 1934 October 26 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 1)
  - Junior News, 1934 November 2 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 1)
  - Junior News, 1934 November 2 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 1)
  - Junior News, 1934 November 9 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 1)
  - Junior News, 1934 November 16 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 1)
  - Junior News, 1934 November 23 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 1)
  - Junior News, 1934 December 7 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 1)
  - Junior News, 1934 December 14 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 1)
  - Junior News, 1934 December 14 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 1)
  - Junior News, 1935 January 11 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 2)
  - Junior News, 1935 January 11 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 2)
  - Junior News, 1935 January 18 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 2)
  - Junior News, 1935 January 18 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 2)
  - Junior News, 1935 February 8 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 2)
  - Junior News, 1935 February 15 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 2)
  - Junior News, 1935 February 15 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 2)
  - Junior News, 1935 March 1 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 2)
  - Junior News, 1935 March 8 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 2)
  - Junior News, 1935 March 15 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 2)
  - Junior News, 1935 March 22 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 2)
  - Junior News, 1935 March 22 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 2)
  - Junior News, 1935 March 29 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 2)
  - Junior News, 1935 April 5 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 2)
  - Junior News, 1935 April 12 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 2)
  - Junior News, 1935 April 18 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 2)
  - Junior News, 1935 May 3 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 2)
  - Junior News, 1935 May 10 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 2)
  - Junior News, 1935 May 31 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 2)
  - Junior News, 1935 October 18 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 2)
  - Junior News, 1935 October 25 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 2)
  - Junior News, 1935 October 25 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 2)
  - Junior News, 1935 November 1 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 2)
  - Junior News, 1935 November 8 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 2)
  - Junior News, 1935 November 15 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 2)
  - Junior News, 1935 November 22 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 2)
  - Junior News, 1935 November 27 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 2)
  - Junior News, 1935 December 6 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 2)
  - Junior News, 1935 December 13 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 2)
  - Junior News, 1935 December 20 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 2)
  - Junior News, 1936 January 10 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 2)
  - Junior News, 1936 January 17 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 2)
  - Junior News, 1936 January 24 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 2)
  - Junior News, 1936 February 14 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 2)
  - Junior News, 1936 March 27 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 2)
  - Junior News, 1936 April 3 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 2)
  - Junior News, 1936 April 24 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 2)
  - Junior News, 1936 May 1 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 2)
  - Junior News, 1936 May 8 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 2)
  - Junior News, 1936 May 14 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 2)
  - Junior News, 1936 May 29 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 2)
  - Junior News, 1936 June 5 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 2)
  - Junior News, 1936 October 3 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 2)
  - Junior News, 1936 October 30 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 2)
  - Junior News, 1936 November 6 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 2)
  - Junior News, 1936 November 13 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 2)
  - Junior News, 1936 November 20 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 2)
  - Junior News, 1936 December 4 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 2)
  - Junior News, 1936 December 11 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 2)
  - Junior News, 1936 December 18 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 2)
  - Junior News, 1937 January 8 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 2)
  - Junior News, 1937 January 15 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 2)
  - Junior News, 1937 January 22 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 2)
  - Junior News, 1937 February 19 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 2)
  - Junior News, 1937 February 26 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 2)
  - Junior News, 1937 March 6 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 2)
  - Junior News, 1937 March 12 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 2)
  - Junior News, 1937 March 19 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 2)
  - Junior News, 1937 April 9 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 2)
  - Junior News, 1937 April 16 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 2)
  - Junior News, 1937 April 23 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 2)
  - Junior News, 1937 April 30 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 2)
  - Junior News, 1937 May 7 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 2)
  - Junior News, 1937 May 7 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 2)
  - Junior News, 1937 May 14 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 2)
  - Junior News, 1937 October 15 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 3)
  - Junior News, 1937 October 22 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 3)
  - Junior News, 1937 November 5 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 3)
  - Junior News, 1937 November 19 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 3)
  - Junior News, 1937 December 10 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 3)
  - Junior News, 1937 December 17 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 3)
  - Junior News, 1938 January 7 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 3)
  - Junior News, 1938 January 14 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 3)
  - Junior News, 1938 January 21 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 3)
  - Junior News, 1938 January 28 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 3)
  - Junior News, 1938 February 18 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 3)
  - Junior News, 1938 February 25 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 3)
  - Junior News, 1938 March 4 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 3)
  - Junior News, 1938 March 18 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 3)
  - Junior News, 1938 March 25 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 3)
  - Junior News, 1938 April 1 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 3)
  - Junior News, 1938 April 8 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 3)
  - Junior News, 1938 April 29 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 3)
  - Junior News, 1938 May 13 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 3)
  - Junior News, 1938 May 20 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 3)
  - Junior News, 1938 May 27 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 3)
  - Junior News, 1938 October 7 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 3)
  - Junior News, 1938 October 28 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 3)
  - Junior News, 1938 November 4 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 3)
  - Junior News, 1938 November 11 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 3)
  - Junior News, 1938 December 2 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 3)
  - Junior News, 1938 December 9 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 3)
  - Junior News, 1938 December 16 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 3)
  - Junior News, 1939 January 6 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 3)
  - Junior News, 1939 January 13 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 3)
  - Junior News, 1939 January 20 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 3)
  - Junior News, 1939 February 10 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 3)
  - Junior News, 1939 February 17 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 3)
  - Junior News, 1939 February 24 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 3)
  - Junior News, 1939 March 3 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 3)
  - Junior News, 1939 March 10 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 3)
  - Junior News, 1939 March 17 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 3)
  - Junior News, 1939 March 24 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 3)
  - Junior News, 1939 April 5 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 3)
  - Junior News, 1939 April 21 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 3)
  - Junior News, 1939 April 28 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 3)
  - Junior News, 1939 May 5 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 3)
  - Junior News, 1939 May 12 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 3)
  - Junior News, 1939 May 19 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 3)
  - Junior News, 1939 May 26 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 3)
  - Junior News, 1939 June 2 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 3)
  - Junior News, 1939 October 13 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 4)
  - Junior News, 1939 October 20 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 4)
  - Junior News, 1939 October 27 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 4)
  - Junior News, 1939 November 3 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 4)
  - Junior News, 1939 November 10 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 4)
  - Junior News, 1939 November 13 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 4)
  - Junior News, 1939 November 17 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 4)
  - Junior News, 1939 November 22 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 4)
  - Junior News, 1939 December 1 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 4)
  - Junior News, 1939 December 8 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 4)
  - Junior News, 1939 December 15 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 4)
  - Junior News, 1940 January 5 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 4)
  - Junior News, 1940 January 12 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 4)
  - Junior News, 1940 January 19 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 4)
  - Junior News, 1940 January 26 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 4)
  - Junior News, 1940 February 16 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 4)
  - Junior News, 1940 February 23 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 4)
  - Junior News, 1940 March 1 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 4)
  - Junior News, 1940 March 8 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 4)
  - Junior News, 1940 April 5 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 4)
  - Junior News, 1940 April 12 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 4)
  - Junior News, 1940 April 19 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 4)
  - Junior News, 1940 April 26 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 4)
  - Junior News, 1940 May 3 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 4)
  - Junior News, 1940 May 10 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 4)
  - Junior News, 1940 May 17 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 4)
  - Junior News, 1940 June 6 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 5)
  - Junior News, 1940 October 4 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 5)
  - Junior News, 1940 October 11 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 5)
  - Junior News, 1940 October 18 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 5)
  - Junior News, 1940 October 25 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 5)
  - Junior News, 1940 November 1 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 5)
  - Junior News, 1940 November 8 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 5)
  - Junior News, 1940 November 20 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 5)
  - Junior News, 1940 November 29 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 5)
  - Junior News, 1940 December 6 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 5)
  - Junior News, 1940 December 13 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 5)
  - Junior News, 1940 December 20 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 5)
  - Junior News, 1941 January 10 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 5)
  - Junior News, 1941 January 17 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 5)
  - Junior News, 1941 February 7 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 5)
  - Junior News, 1941 February 14 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 5)
  - Junior News, 1941 February 21 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 5)
  - Junior News, 1941 February 28 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 5)
  - Junior News, 1941 March 7 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 5)
  - Junior News, 1941 March 14 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 5)
  - Junior News, 1941 March 21 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 5)
  - Junior News, 1941 March 28 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 5)
  - Junior News, 1941 April 9 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 5)
  - Junior News, 1941 April 25 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 5)
  - Junior News, 1941 May 2 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 5)
  - Junior News, 1941 May 9 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 5)
  - Junior News, 1941 May 24 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 5)
- Memoribilia, 1935-2004; Undated; 15; 1.6 cubic ft.
  Collection is arranged in the original order it was donated in.
  Series consists of materials related to student life at the Milne School, with pieces such as school uniforms, sports gear, information related to reunion planning, diplomas, and other awards.
- Milne Library Preservation Project Photographs, ca. 2003
  Contains digital images of the restored murals and friezes in Milne 200 on the UAlbany Downtown Campus, which was used as the Milne School Library.
  Biographical / Historical
  David Cunningham Lithgow created the 14 murals on the walls of the Milne School Library beginning in 1935. The murals are painted on canvas attached to the wall and depict scence from the history of the Albany area. Lithgow was allegedly a friend of President Abram Brubacher. The friezes were created by Bertel Thorvaldsen, beginning in 1929. The murals were restored beginning in 2003.
  - "The Mahikan Indian People" Milne 200 Mural, 1933 September
  - "In the Year 1609 Henry Hudson sailed His Vessel, "Milne 200 Mural, 1933 September
  - "Heyward and His Female Companions" Milne 200 Mural, 1933 September
  - "Albany as a Trading Post About 1685" Milne 200 Mural, 1933 September
  - "Governor Thomas Dongan" Milne 200 Mural, 1937 November
  - "The Courtship of Alexander Hamilton and Elizabeth Schuyler" Milne 200 Mural, 1939 September
  - "The Anti-Ratification Riot in Albany, 1788" Milne 200 Mural, 1940 October
  - "Robert Fulton's Clermont Arrived in Albany, Sept. 5th, 1807" Milne 200 Mural, 1941 October
  - "The Erie Canal's First Boat Seneca Chief Arrived at Albany, Nov. 2nd, 1825" Milne 200 Mural, 1943 October
  - "The Locomotive DeWitt Clinton First Trip Albany to Schenectady Sept. 24, 1831" Milne 200 Mural, 1943 October
  - "An Incident of Anti-Rentism" Milne 200 Mural, 1935 October
  - "Normal School Building Corner of Lodge and Howard Sts. Albany N. Y. Erected 1849" Milne 200 Mural, 1943 October